expressupdate.com 2015-03-26

# Privacy Policy

### Infogroup Inc. Online and Offline Privacy Policy

Infogroup helps companies increase sales and customer loyalty through our high-value data, market intelligence and innovative digital solutions. We uncover and unlock revenue growth by enabling our clients - from local businesses to Fortune 100 companies - to connect and engage with their most valuable audiences millions of times each day. Infogroup data powers the top 5 Internet search engines and provides point-of-interest data for the leading in-car navigation systems.   
Infogroup recognizes the privacy interests of the businesses and consumers on which it collects information and has implemented comprehensive and formal data protection policies which balance privacy expectations with the legitimate business need of our customers. 

### Data Compilation

The information compiled by Infogroup incorporates several data elements for businesses and consumers. The information is acquired from reliable sources and Infogroup takes great care through specific quality control procedures to verify and maintain the accuracy of the information. 

### Security

Infogroup uses several security systems and procedures to safeguard the information, ensuring the data is accessed only by authorized individuals for legitimate business needs. Infogroup will not transmit or sell the compiled information to third parties without obtaining a written or electronic agreement that defines the rights and responsibilities with respect to the data. Further, Infogroup will review our customer's use of the data to ensure sensitive data is being handled in accordance with required protections, and that this information is not used for deceptive, misleading, distasteful, or suspicious purposes. 

### Compliance

Infogroup complies with all applicable federal and state laws concerning data privacy, as well as best practices and procedures and guidelines established by industry groups of which the company is a contributing member, including the Direct Marketing Association (DMA). Infogroup maintains agreements with its customers containing strict controls on the data as required by the applicable laws and industry standards. The company also encourages its customers that are not members of the DMA or other applicable industry groups to comply with the standards and guidelines established by those groups. 

### Communication, Access, and Correction

Upon a reasonable request, Infogroup will explain to businesses and consumers the nature and types of sources used to compile the data. Infogroup maintains procedures by which businesses can request corrections for any incorrect data, as well as request any business or consumer information be suppressed from compiled lists which are marketed to Infogroup customers. Requests for information or access can be made in writing to Infogroup Inc., Attn: Content Feedback, 1020 E First St, Papillion, NE 68046 or [contentfeedback@infogroup.com](mailto:contentfeedback@infogroup.com). 

### Privacy

Infogroup Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Infogroup Inc. believes that concern for everyone's privacy is a basis for sound business practices within direct marketing and other arenas. This statement is intended to apply to all visitors of web sites owned and operated by Infogroup Inc. If you have any questions after reading this privacy statement, you may contact us at 800.321.0869. 

Infogroup Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Infogroup Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Infogroup Inc.’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. 

### Collection of Information

Infogroup Inc. does not collect personally identifiable information about visitors except when visitors specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from the registration process for subscription sites or services and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and bulletin boards), suggestions, and transactional areas. Such information may be used by Infogroup Inc. for the following purposes: contacting a subscriber regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement, special discounts, promotions, products offered and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. 

Infogroup Inc. values opinions and comments from visitors, so we occasionally conduct online surveys. These surveys are entirely optional for all visitors. Most frequently, the information is aggregated and used to make improvements to Infogroup Inc. web sites and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for visitors. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey. Infogroup Inc. reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of visitor's behavior and characteristics. In order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of visitors that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. Infogroup Inc. will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. Also, visitors should be aware that Infogroup Inc. may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through an Infogroup Inc. web site.   
Infogroup Inc. is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and visitors should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information. Visitors should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas of Infogroup Inc. sites, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in the visitor's communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties. This information may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Infogroup Inc. 

### Cookies, etc.

Visitors also should be aware that non-personal information (for example, domain names or e-mail and IP addresses) and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of Infogroup Inc.'s internet servers or at Infogroup Inc.'s discretion through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate a visitor's ongoing access to and use of the site, track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Visitors to Infogroup Inc. web sites should be aware that Infogroup Inc. cannot control the use of cookies, or the non-personal information collected through the cookies by advertisers or third parties hosting data for Infogroup Inc. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature. However, visitors should note that cookies may be necessary to provide them with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Infogroup Inc. web sites. 

### Opt Out Policy

Upon a visitor's request, Infogroup Inc. will: 

Allow any visitor to "opt out" of further promotional contacts;Use reasonable efforts to allow visitors to update/correct personal information previously submitted which he/she states is erroneous to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests; andInitiate reasonable efforts to functionally delete the visitor and his/her personal information from its database. Visitors should be aware that it might be impossible to completely delete erroneous information or a visitor's personal information without some residual information remaining in its database because of backups and records of deletions. 

### Security

Infogroup Inc. is responsible for the security of personal information provided by visitors. Strict measures will be taken to assure against unauthorized access, alteration, or dissemination of personal information. 

### Disclosure of Information

Infogroup Inc. may disclose visitor information if requested or required to by law, court order, or government or law enforcement authority. In addition, Infogroup Inc. may in its sole discretion disclose visitor information if it believes in good faith that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable for any reason including without limitation rights or properties of Infogroup Inc. or any third party. 

### Changes

Infogroup Inc. reserves the right to change this privacy statement at anytime upon providing notification to visitors. This privacy statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any other person or entity.   
A notice will be posted on Infogroup's web page [www.infogroup.com](http://www.infogroup.com/). 

EFFECTIVE DATE: January 1, 2010
